// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of these is not an intermolecular force?",
    answer: "a. covalent bonding",
    options: [
      "a. covalent bonding",
      "b. London dispersion forces",
      "c. hydrogen bonding",
      "d. Dipole-dipole forces"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What type of IMF is present in all substances, regardless of polarity?",
    answer: "a. London dispersion forces",
    options: [
      "a. London dispersion forces",
      "b. ion-dipole forces",
      "c. Dipole-dipole forces",
      "d. hydrogen bonding"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Intermolecular forces are the forces __________.",
    answer: "c. between molecules",
    options: [
      "a. within molecules",
      "b. between substances",
      "c. between molecules",
      "d. within substances"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the strongest intermolecular force below?",
    answer: "b. hydrogen bonding",
    options: [
      "a. ion-dipole",
      "b. hydrogen bonding",
      "c. London dispersion",
      "d. Dipole-dipole"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What explains the very high melting and boiling point of water?",
    answer: "c. Strong hydrogen bonds between water molecules.",
    options: [
      "a. Strong dipole-dipole bonds between water molecules",
      "b. Dispersion forces which are present in all molecules.",
      "c. Strong hydrogen bonds between water molecules.",
      "d. Asymmetrical shape of the polar bonds."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Hydrogen bonding occurs when hydrogen is bonded to N, O, or F. Which of the following has hydrogen bonding?",
    answer: "d. NH3",
    options: [
      "a. CBr4",
      "b. H2S",
      "c. NO2",
      "d. NH3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is the second strongest intermolecular force, after hydrogen bonding?",
    answer: "a. Dipole-dipole",
    options: [
      "a. Dipole-dipole",
      "b. hydrogen bonding",
      "c. ion-dipole",
      "d. London dispersion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which substance would have the weakest intermolecular forces of attraction?",
    answer: "a. CH4",
    options: [
      "a. CH4",
      "b. H2O",
      "c. NaCl",
      "d. MgF2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Ionic bonding involves _________.",
    answer: "b. transfer of electrons",
    options: [
      "a. transfer of protons",
      "b. transfer of electrons",
      "c. transfer of neutrons",
      "d. none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The interaction between molecules (substances that are made of atoms that bond through the sharing of electrons to form covalent bonds) is called _________.",
    answer: "a. Intermolecular forces",
    options: [
      "a. Intermolecular forces",
      "b. hydrogen bonding",
      "c. Dipole-dipole forces",
      "d. London dispersion forces"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];